ericthecarguy.com 2014-06-23

# Eric The Car Guy- Stay Dirty! - Eric The Car Guy- Stay Dirty!

##  [ Privacy Policy](http://www.ericthecarguy.com/component/content/article/8-main-page/41-privacy-policy)

User Rating:  / 56

PRIVACY POLICY  
Updated: May 27, 2011

EricTheCarGuy ("EricTheCarGuy", "we", "our" or "us") understands that you care how information about you is gathered, used and shared. This Privacy Policy describes how the information collected when you use EricTheCarGuy.com and related services (the "Service") will be used and how you can control the collection, correction and deletion of information. Questions regarding this policy should be directed to "Info" at [](mailto:%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'ma'%20+%20'il'%20+%20'to';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy69096%20=%20'biz'%20+%20'@';%20addy69096%20=%20addy69096%20+%20'ericthecarguy'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\('%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20':'%20+%20addy69096%20+%20'\\'%3E'\);%20document.write\(addy69096\);%20document.write\('%3C\\/a%3E'\);%20//--%3E\\n%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20email%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it.%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3C/'\);%20document.write\('span%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E.)[biz@ericthecarguy.com](mailto:biz@ericthecarguy.com).

INFORMATION COLLECTED BY US

User Provided Information: You provide us information about yourself and the vehicle(s) you drive, such as your name and email address, the year, make, model, sub-model, mileage, vehicle identification number ("VIN") and maintenance history when you register with the Service. Any electronic correspondence with us may be retained.

Site Activity: We follow some of the actions you take on EricTheCarGuy.com, such as watching a video, uploading Content or referring a friend.

Cookies and other Non-Edible, but Tasty Sounding Information Collection Processes: When you visit EricTheCarGuy.com, we may send one or more small non-executable text files to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets us help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site (aka: cookie). A cookie does not collect personal information about you and we use both session cookies and persistent cookies. We also use clear GIFs (aka: web beacons), JavaScript and Log File Information that may collect and store your IP address. All of this stuff is used to facilitate more accurate reporting, improve the EricTheCarGuy.com experience and help us diagnose and repair problems with our Service. EricTheCarGuy may use Google Analytics or Mixpanel to enhance our understanding of use of the Service. Google Analytics and Mixpanel collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, including cookies and your IP address. Google Analytics and Mixpanel also receive this information and their use of it is governed by their privacy policies.

Third Party Log In Credentials: By logging into the Site using a set of Third Party Credentials (such as Facebook), you will be giving us access to certain general personally identifying information stored in your profiles. We do not view this information without first obtaining your consent. In some instances we will provide you tools to share our Service with other people in your networks. We encourage, and may record, the frequency of this activity.

HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

If you submit personal information to EricTheCarGuy.com, we may use that information to operate, maintain and improve the features and functionality of the Service. Personal information or content that you voluntarily submit to the Service becomes available to the public.

We do not use your email address or other personal information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent. We will use your email address to send you notices regarding the Service. If you wish to opt out of email communication from EricTheCarGuy.com, send an email to info "at" [support@ericthecarguy.com](mailto:support@ericthecarguy.com) with the words "Opt Out of Email" in the subject line. Please note that opting out may prevent you from receiving important messages regarding the Service.

We use cookies, web beacons and log file information to i) store information that allows you to log in automatically the next time you use the Service; ii) provide customized and personalized content; iii) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing efforts; iv) monitor metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed; and v) track your submissions.

HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION

When you create an account on our Service, some information about your account and your account activity are provided to other users of the Service. This may include the date you created your account, your member name, the videos you submitted, comments and updates you submitted, your name, location, expertise, certifications, interests and favorite car. Should you choose to submit information about your shop to EricTheCarGuy.com, we may display your shop name, address and description, the hours, makes, specialties, amenities offered, affiliations, labor rates and hours of operation.

Your EricTheCarGuy.com user name, not your email address, is displayed to other users of the site when you submit content. Content submitted to our Service may be distributed through the internet and other media and may be viewed by EricTheCarGuy.com users or the general public.

DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

EricTheCarGuy may share your personally identifiable information with third parties solely for the purpose of providing services to you. If this is done, third parties' use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Policy. We may disclose personally identifiable information: i) if we have a good faith belief that doing so is required by a subpoena or other judicial or administrative order or otherwise required by law; ii) to enforce our Terms of Service, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend ourselves against any third party claims or allegations or to protect the security or integrity of our Service; and iii) to exercise or protects the rights or property of EricTheCarGuy or our users.

We may share non-personally identifiable information such as anonymous usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, etc. with interested third parties.

We may allow third-party ad servers or ad networks (such as Google AdSense) to display advertisements on our Service. These third-party ad servers or ad networks may use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements that appear within the Site. When this happens, they automatically receive your IP address and other log file information. These third-party companies may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize their advertising content. We do not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent.

THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

The Site may contain links to services and websites provided by third parties. We are not responsible for the practices employed by web sites linked to or from our Site nor the information or content contained therein. Any Personal Information provided to third-party sites or services is governed by that party's privacy and security.

HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION

We use commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your Personal Information. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to our Service and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, we make commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical or managerial safeguards.

MINORS

The privacy of young children is especially important to us. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register on our Site. If you are under 13, you are not permitted under the Terms of Use to use our Service; please do not send any information about yourself to us and stop using our service. In the event that we learn that personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, has been collected by us, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you are between the ages of 13 and 18, please ask your parent or guardian's permission before using the Site and our Services.

CHANGES IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may update or amend this Privacy Policy at any time, with or without advance notice. In the event there are material changes in the way we treat your Personal Information, or in the Privacy Policy itself, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

Please direct any comments or questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site or any other matter to us at info "at" [support@ericthecarguy.com](mailto:support@ericthecarguy.com) or by mail at EricTheCarGuy P.O. Box 395 Kings Mills, OH 45034.
